aaasouth.com 2017-02-28

# AAA Auto Club Group - Privacy Policy

At AAA, maintaining your trust and confidence is our top priority. We do not sell or rent nonpublic personal information about our members or former members. We do not share non-public personal information about our members or former members with companies outside of AAA, except where required or permitted by law. We carefully manage and safeguard information among our companies and affiliates, based on your membership or other relationships with AAA, in order to provide you with unsurpassed service, greater convenience and superior value.

Sources from which we may collect nonpublic information about you include: information we receive from you on applications or other forms in writing, via facsimile transmission, by telephone, by electronic means including e-mail and our website, or by other means of communication; information resulting from your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; information resulting from entitled services that you have received from us, our affiliates or others; information obtained from governmental sources, such as your driving record and claims history (insurance clients); and information obtained from non-governmental sources, such as demographic data used for marketing purposes.

We may disclose personally identifiable information about you to persons or organizations within or outside of the AAA Federation as permitted or required by law including companies that perform marketing services for us or with whom we have joint marketing agreements. These agreements allow us to extend the value of your membership or provide you with special savings. Information will normally be limited to name, address, telephone number, membership or customer number and Club tenure. Under certain circumstances, additional information will be provided to appropriate third parties with your consent or at your direction, such as when you apply for a loan, request a quote for insurance or, as necessary, to perform other services. Information will also be disclosed, if necessary, to effect, administer or enforce a transaction, benefit or service that you have requested or authorized or to which you are entitled. This includes such information as the description, location and license number of your vehicle, as well as your telephone contact number and other information deemed necessary to provide you with emergency road service. Information may be shared among the Club’s corporate affiliates and subsidiaries, other AAA Clubs and the AAA National Office. Other third parties with whom information may be shared include, but are not limited to, emergency road service contractors, AAA Approved Auto Repair facilities, travel service providers, financial service providers, insurance support organizations, insurance agents, claims representatives, independent contractors, courts and governmental agencies.

We restrict access to your nonpublic information to those employees who need such information in order to provide products or services to you. In compliance with federal regulations, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to guard and prevent misuse of your nonpublic personal information.

## Internet Privacy Policy

AAA is committed to honoring the privacy of the users of the AAA Web Site, which includes any personally identifiable information. AAA will utilize any information collected to better understand its users’ needs and provide better service. In addition, AAA will use the information it gathers to improve the content of the Web site. If any personally identifiable information has been volunteered, AAA may utilize that information to notify users about updates to the Web site and/or contact users for marketing purposes. The information that is personally identifiable will not be shared with or sold to any other organizations for commercial purposes. 

Below is a list of non-volunteered information that will be collected automatically when visiting the AAA Web Site: 

  * The referrer (the site prior to entering the AAA Web site)
  * The IP address of the workstation
  * Date and time logged in and out
  * Pages visited while on our site
  * Time spent on each page
  * Files downloaded
  * Criteria used when searching

If the user supplies their telephone number online, they may be contacted by AAA regarding orders placed online. Please be sure to provide AAA with the correct phone number.

Entering the zip code upon initial visit to the AAA web site will cause a cookie to be written to the PC in use at the time. This will allow the AAA web site to automatically route subsequent visits to the user’s local AAA club.

Using the automatic log-in function of this website will cause a cookie to be written to the PC in use at the time. Cookies are small text files which store an encrypted version of your user ID and password. When you come back to this site, this information will be used to automatically log you into the web site using a secure connection. The cookies will not store any information that will be used for tracking or advertising.

To avoid any solicitations from AAA as a result of establishing a User ID on this website, please click on "My Account" at the top of this page, log in, and set your communication preferences (email, telephone, and/or mail).
